Guide to the Jack and Rebecca Matlock Papers, 1930s-2017 RL.11082
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Audiovisual Materials, 1980-2016; 740 items
  - Interviews
    - JFM Briefs Mathias Del San (?), undated (Box AV07, Audio-cassette RL11082-CS-0010)
      - Digital audio file (Digital-materials RL11082-SET-0011, Audio-file RL11082-CS-0010.mp3)
    - Mrs. Matlock Interview for Department of State Oral History Project, undated (Box AV07, Audio-cassette RL11082-CS-0017)
      - Digital audio file (Digital-materials RL11082-SET-0018, Audio-file RL11082-CS-0017.mp3)
    - Ambassador Matlock's Interview w/ NY Times Sonya Kishkovsky, undated (Box AV07, Audio-cassette RL11082-CS-0024)
      - Digital audio file (Digital-materials RL11082-SET-0025, Audio-file RL11082-CS-0024.mp3)
    - Ambassador Jack F. Matlock, Jr. Interview-"60 Minutes", undated (Box AV11, Audio-cassette RL11082-CS-0163)
      - Digital audio file (Digital-materials RL11082-SET-0164, Audio-file RL11082-CS-0163.mp3)
    - Ambassador-Jack F. Matlock, Jr. Interview - Graphics News Service (Poor Quality), undated (Box AV13, Audio-cassette RL11082-CS-0209)
      - Digital audio file (Digital-materials RL11082-SET-0210, Audio-file RL11082-CS-0209.mp3)
    - Interviews with Russian Writers-cheifly emigres-conducted by: John Glad, Ph.D., Germanic & Slavic Department, University of Maryland, undated (Box AV02, Video-cassette RL11082-VHS-0062)
      - Digital video file (Digital-materials RL11082-SET-0468, Video-file RL11082-VHS-0062.mp4)
    - "Discovering America," interview with Matlock at Sparo, undated (Box AV20, Video-cassette RL11082-VHS-0241)
    - Interview - "Getting to Know You" Ambassador Jack F. Matlock, Jr., NERVE Film company, 45 minutes - On Exchanges, undated (Box AV20, Video-cassette RL11082-VHS-0253)
  - Lectures, Speeches, and Remarks
    - George F. Kennan Talk in Moscow on background of Franco-Russian Entente, 1981-04-16 (Box AV15, Audio-cassette RL11082-CS-0290)
      - Digital audio file (Digital-materials RL11082-SET-0291, Audio-file RL11082-CS-0293.mp3)
    - Ambassador Matlock Masaryk Wreath-Laying, 1982-03-07 (Box AV15, Audio-cassette RL11082-CS-0291)
      - Digital audio file (Digital-materials RL11082-SET-0292, Audio-file RL11082-CS-0294.mp3)
    - Side A- March 7, 1982 LANY, VOA-Ambassador's Remarks, 1982-03-07 (Box AV15, Audio-cassette RL11082-CS-0292)
      - Digital audio file (Digital-materials RL11082-SET-0293, Audio-file RL11082-CS-0295.mp3)
    - VOA Czechoslovak Svc (includes Matlock speech at Cheb. Czechoslovakia), TAC-82-05-15, 1982-05-15 (Box AV15, Audio-cassette RL11082-CS-0282)
      - Digital audio file (Digital-materials RL11082-SET-0283, Audio-file RL11082-CS-0283.mp3)
    - Matlock Pre-recorded remarks for Cheb wreath-laying, 1982-05-15 (Box AV15, Audio-cassette RL11082-CS-0289)
      - Digital audio file (Digital-materials RL11082-SET-0290, Audio-file RL11082-CS-0291.mp3)
    - VOA Broadcast Speech, TAC-82-07-04, 1982-07-04 (Box AV15, Audio-cassette RL11082-CS-0279)
      - Digital audio file (Digital-materials RL11082-SET-0280, Audio-file RL11082-CS-0280.mp3)
    - Matlock Address to Soviet People, Index Number TVS-87-07-04, 1987-07-04 (Box AV02, Video-cassette RL11082-VHS-0053)
      - Digital video file (Digital-materials RL11082-SET-0459, Video-file RL11082-VHS-0053.mp4)
    - Ambassador Jack Matlock's appearance on VREMYA, 1987-07-04 (Box AV20, Video-cassette RL11082-VHS-0239)
    - TCA-88-03-05 Matlock Talk on SDI, 1988-03-05 (Box AV17, Audio-cassette RL11082-CS-0372)
      - Digital audio file (Digital-materials RL11082-SET-0372, Audio-file RL11082-CS-0375.mp3)
    - TCA-88-03-24 Speech to Kennan Institute, 1988-03-24 (Box AV17, Audio-cassette RL11082-CS-0358)
      - Digital audio file (Digital-materials RL11082-SET-0358, Audio-file RL11082-CS-0361.mp3)
    - TCA-11-03-25Speech to Arden House Conference, Arden House, Harriman NY, 1988-03-25 (Box AV17, Audio-cassette RL11082-CS-0355)
      - Digital audio file (Digital-materials RL11082-SET-0355, Audio-file RL11082-CS-0358.mp3)
    - TCA-88-03-27A University of Miami 1) Luncheon Speech, Faculty Club, 2) Q&A, 3) Press Conference, 1988-03-27 (Box AV17, Audio-cassette RL11082-CS-0356)
      - Digital audio file (Digital-materials RL11082-SET-0356, Audio-file RL11082-CS-0359.mp3)
    - TCA-88-03-27B University of MiamiSpeech to Graduate Students and Visitors, 1988-03-27 (Box AV17, Audio-cassette RL11082-CS-0357)
      - Digital audio file (Digital-materials RL11082-SET-0357, Audio-file RL11082-CS-0360.mp3)
    - Matlock Address, Soviet TV, 1988-07-04 (Box AV19, Video-cassette RL11082-VHS-0184)
    - Ambassador Matlock's July 4, 1988 remarks on Soviet television's "Vremya" program. Note attached: "Mr. Ambassador, Here is a tape of your July 4 remarks. The Shmelyov's were at dinner last night and we watched you on TV. They had complimentary words to pass on. - Margo S.", 1988-07-04 (Box AV20, Video-cassette RL11082-VHS-0237)
    - "Entering the CITI Program," Ambassador Jack F. Matlock, Jr., U.S. Ambassador to the Soviet Union, Professional Development Ctr., Pompano Beach, Fla., 1988-11-09 (Box AV21, Video-cassette RL11082-VHS-0255)
    - Jack Matlock Grimsley High School talk, 1989-03-31 (Box AV14, Audio-cassette RL11082-CS-0246)
      - Digital audio file (Digital-materials RL11082-SET-0247, Audio-file RL11082-CS-0246.mp3)
    - Ambassador Matlock, Greensboro College, 1989-04-05 (Box AV19, Video-cassette RL11082-VHS-0187)
    - Vremya with Ambassador Matlock's remarks, 1989-07-04 (Box AV20, Video-cassette RL11082-VHS-0243)
    - Rebecca Matlock, Jack Matlock, interview and statement, 1989-07-04 (Box AV20, Video-cassette RL11082-VHS-0246)
    - Ambassador Matlock at MGU, 1989-11-01 (Box AV08, Audio-cassette RL11082-CS-0048)
      - Digital audio file (Digital-materials RL11082-SET-0049, Audio-file RL11082-CS-0048.mp3)
    - Kishinev Speech (Normal), Romanian, For: Romanian SVC, Voice of America, USIA, 1990-03-29 (Box AV08, Audio-cassette RL11082-CS-0042)
      - Digital audio file (Digital-materials RL11082-SET-0043, Audio-file RL11082-CS-0042.mp3)
    - Kishinev Speech (Slow), Romanian, For: Romanian SVC, Voice of America, USIA, 1990-03-29 (Box AV08, Audio-cassette RL11082-CS-0043)
      - Digital audio file (Digital-materials RL11082-SET-0044, Audio-file RL11082-CS-0043.mp3)
    - Ambassador Matlock at Kishinev State University, 1990-05-05 (Box AV13, Audio-cassette RL11082-CS-0220)
      - Digital audio file (Digital-materials RL11082-SET-0221, Audio-file RL11082-CS-0220.mp3)
    - Kazakh translation--fast, medium, and slow speed--of Ambassador Matlock remarks at Opening Design Exhibit in Alma Ata, version 2, 1990-06 (Box AV15, Audio-cassette RL11082-CS-0273)
      - Digital audio file (Digital-materials RL11082-SET-0274, Audio-file RL11082-CS-0274.mp3)
    - Talk and Q & A at MGIMO, 1990-11-26 (Box AV13, Audio-cassette RL11082-CS-0206)
      - Digital audio file (Digital-materials RL11082-SET-0207, Audio-file RL11082-CS-0206.mp3)
    - Ambassador's Remarks to Committee of War Veterans, 1990-11-28 (Box AV13, Audio-cassette RL11082-CS-0208)
      - Digital audio file (Digital-materials RL11082-SET-0209, Audio-file RL11082-CS-0208.mp3)
    - John Bowlt Lecture in Russia at Spaso House, Session on Malevich, March 26, 1991, 1991-03-26 (Box AV07, Audio-cassette RL11082-CS-0008)
      - Digital audio file (Digital-materials RL11082-SET-0009, Audio-file RL11082-CS-0008.mp3)
    - Ligachev, Harriman Lecture, 1991-11-07 (Box AV08, Audio-cassette RL11082-CS-0047)
      - Digital audio file (Digital-materials RL11082-SET-0048, Audio-file RL11082-CS-0047.mp3)
    - Dean's Day Address, Col. Univ., 1992-03 (Box AV22, Audio-cassette RL11082-MCS-0044)
    - Plattsburgh, NY (SUNY), 1992-04-15 (Box AV22, Audio-cassette RL11082-MCS-0046)
    - Monadnock Summer Lyceum-J.F. Matlock, Jr. "Post Soviet…", 1992-07-05 (Box AV07, Audio-cassette RL11082-CS-0014)
      - Digital audio file (Digital-materials RL11082-SET-0015, Audio-file RL11082-CS-0014.mp3)
    - Jack Matlock−Dickey Lecture, 1992-07-21 (Box AV07, Audio-cassette RL11082-CS-0004)
      - Digital audio file (Digital-materials RL11082-SET-0005, Audio-file RL11082-CS-0004.mp3)
    - Matlock, Lecture on Islamic States to Sue to ????, 1992-08 (Box AV18, Audio-cassette RL11082-CS-0380)
      - Digital audio file (Digital-materials RL11082-SET-0380, Audio-file RL11082-MCS-0003.mp3)
    - Jack Matlock−Dickey Lecture, 1992-08-13 (Box AV07, Audio-cassette RL11082-CS-0012)
      - Digital audio file (Digital-materials RL11082-SET-0013, Audio-file RL11082-CS-0012.mp3)
    - Speech to NY Teachers on Post-Soviet Transition, 1994-10-29 (Box AV22, Audio-cassette RL11082-MCS-0055)
    - 29 Apr 95 - Dean's Day Keynote, Col. Univ. Alumni in Wash DC; Kenan Institute "Current Issues in Russ. Politics," 1 May 95, 1995-04-29; 1995-05-01 (Box AV22, Audio-cassette RL11082-MCS-0040)
    - Chautauqua Institution Lecture Jack F. Matlock, Jr., 1996-01-14 (Box AV14, Audio-cassette RL11082-CS-0265)
      - Digital audio file (Digital-materials RL11082-SET-0266, Audio-file RL11082-CS-0266.mp3)
    - Quest for Peace in the 21st Century: Ambassador Jack F. Matlock, University of California Irvine, 2010 (Box AV22, Video-disc RL11082-DVD-0001)
      - Original video-disc (Digital-materials RL11082-SET-0381, Audio-file RL11082-MCS-0005.mp3)
    - VOA Armenian Service, Remarks by Ambassador Matlock, Armenian Text, Voice of America, USIA (tape case has hand-written scrap paper taped to it that reads "Paragraph in Azeri"), undated (Box AV08, Audio-cassette RL11082-CS-0044)
      - Digital audio file (Digital-materials RL11082-SET-0045, Audio-file RL11082-CS-0044.mp3)
    - Matlock's Speech in Latvian, undated (Box AV15, Audio-cassette RL11082-CS-0284)
      - Digital audio file (Digital-materials RL11082-SET-0285, Audio-file RL11082-CS-0286.mp3)
    - President's Speech, undated (Box AV01, Video-cassette RL11082-VHS-0022)
      - Digital video file (Digital-materials RL11082-SET-0430, Video-file RL11082-VHS-0022.mp4)
    - Matlock Speech to IPPNW Moscow, undated (Box AV04, Video-cassette RL11082-VHS-0126)
      - Digital video file (Digital-materials RL11082-SET-0532, Video-file RL11082-VHS-0126.mp4)
    - Lecture by Rebecca Matlock - Com. W. Rus., undated (Box AV22, Audio-cassette RL11082-MCS-0057)
  - Press Briefs
    - Press Conf. in Nizhui Novgorod, 1980-12 (Box AV22, Audio-cassette RL11082-MCS-0045)
    - Matlock Press Conference 2nd Half Backgrounder, 1986-05-15 (Box AV17, Audio-cassette RL11082-CS-0366)
      - Digital audio file (Digital-materials RL11082-SET-0366, Audio-file RL11082-CS-0369.mp3)
    - Ambassador Matlock Backgrounder, 1987-04-17 (Box AV17, Audio-cassette RL11082-CS-0367)
      - Digital audio file (Digital-materials RL11082-SET-0367, Audio-file RL11082-CS-0370.mp3)
    - Amb. Matlock Background to West. Press, 1987-05-29 (Box AV15, Audio-cassette RL11082-CS-0299)
      - Digital audio file (Digital-materials RL11082-SET-0299, Audio-file RL11082-CS-0302.mp3)
    - Matlock on Background, 1987-06-19 (Box AV15, Audio-cassette RL11082-CS-0301)
      - Digital audio file (Digital-materials RL11082-SET-0301, Audio-file RL11082-CS-0304.mp3)
    - Matlock Background, 1987-06-26 (Box AV15, Audio-cassette RL11082-CS-0303)
      - Digital audio file (Digital-materials RL11082-SET-0303, Audio-file RL11082-CS-0306.mp3)
    - Ambassador Matlock Backgrounder, 1987-07-24 (Box AV15, Audio-cassette RL11082-CS-0307)
      - Digital audio file (Digital-materials RL11082-SET-0307, Audio-file RL11082-CS-0310.mp3)
    - Ambassador Matlock Backgrounder with intro on the record, 1987-07-30 (Box AV16, Audio-cassette RL11082-CS-0309)
      - Digital audio file (Digital-materials RL11082-SET-0309, Audio-file RL11082-CS-0312.mp3)
    - Ambassador Matlock Backgrounder, 1987-08-14 (Box AV16, Audio-cassette RL11082-CS-0310)
      - Digital audio file (Digital-materials RL11082-SET-0310, Audio-file RL11082-CS-0313.mp3)
    - Ambassador Matlock Press Briefing, 1987-08-21 (Box AV16, Audio-cassette RL11082-CS-0312)
      - Digital audio file (Digital-materials RL11082-SET-0312, Audio-file RL11082-CS-0315.mp3)
    - Ambassador Matlock Background to U.S. and Western Press, 1987-08-28 (Box AV16, Audio-cassette RL11082-CS-0315)
      - Digital audio file (Digital-materials RL11082-SET-0315, Audio-file RL11082-CS-0318.mp3)
    - Ambassador Matlock's Backgrounder to U.S. Press, 1987-09-01 (Box AV16, Audio-cassette RL11082-CS-0319)
      - Digital audio file (Digital-materials RL11082-SET-0319, Audio-file RL11082-CS-0322.mp3)
    - Ambassador Matlock Background, 1987-09-04 (Box AV16, Audio-cassette RL11082-CS-0317)
      - Digital audio file (Digital-materials RL11082-SET-0317, Audio-file RL11082-CS-0320.mp3)
    - Ambassador Matlock Press Brief, 1987-09-25 (Box AV16, Audio-cassette RL11082-CS-0320)
      - Digital audio file (Digital-materials RL11082-SET-0320, Audio-file RL11082-CS-0323.mp3)
    - Ambassador Matlock briefs St. Louis Press Club, 1987-09-30 (Box AV16, Audio-cassette RL11082-CS-0321)
      - Digital audio file (Digital-materials RL11082-SET-0321, Audio-file RL11082-CS-0324.mp3)
    - Ambassador Matlock Backgrounder, 1987-10-02 (Box AV16, Audio-cassette RL11082-CS-0322)
      - Digital audio file (Digital-materials RL11082-SET-0322, Audio-file RL11082-CS-0325.mp3)
    - Ambassador Matlock Press Brief-U.S. Press, 1987-10-09 (Box AV16, Audio-cassette RL11082-CS-0323)
      - Digital audio file (Digital-materials RL11082-SET-0323, Audio-file RL11082-CS-0326.mp3)
    - Ambassador Press Brief, 1987-10-16 (Box AV16, Audio-cassette RL11082-CS-0326)
      - Digital audio file (Digital-materials RL11082-SET-0326, Audio-file RL11082-CS-0329.mp3)
    - Ambassador Matlock with U.S. Press after Shultz- Tape I, 1987-10-24 (Box AV16, Audio-cassette RL11082-CS-0327)
      - Digital audio file (Digital-materials RL11082-SET-0327, Audio-file RL11082-CS-0330.mp3)
    - Ambassador Matlock with U.S. Press after Shultz- Tape II, 1987-10-24 (Box AV16, Audio-cassette RL11082-CS-0328)
      - Digital audio file (Digital-materials RL11082-SET-0328, Audio-file RL11082-CS-0331.mp3)
    - Ambassador with World Media Assn., 1987-10-26 (Box AV16, Audio-cassette RL11082-CS-0329)
      - Digital audio file (Digital-materials RL11082-SET-0329, Audio-file RL11082-CS-0332.mp3)
    - Ambassador Matlock Press Brief (U.S. & Western Press), 1987-11-02 (Box AV16, Audio-cassette RL11082-CS-0330)
      - Digital audio file (Digital-materials RL11082-SET-0330, Audio-file RL11082-CS-0333.mp3)
    - Ambassador Matlock on-the-record briefing wit Ms. Curcurnia of "La Republica", 1987-11-05 (Box AV16, Audio-cassette RL11082-CS-0331)
      - Digital audio file (Digital-materials RL11082-SET-0331, Audio-file RL11082-CS-0334.mp3)
    - Matlock Press Brief (U.S. & Western Press), 1987-11-06 (Box AV16, Audio-cassette RL11082-CS-0332)
      - Digital audio file (Digital-materials RL11082-SET-0332, Audio-file RL11082-CS-0335.mp3)
    - Ambassador Matlock Briefing with U.S. Press, 1987-11-13 (Box AV16, Audio-cassette RL11082-CS-0333)
      - Digital audio file (Digital-materials RL11082-SET-0333, Audio-file RL11082-CS-0336.mp3)
    - Ambassador Matlock Press Brief, 1987-11-20 (Box AV16, Audio-cassette RL11082-CS-0336)
      - Digital audio file (Digital-materials RL11082-SET-0336, Audio-file RL11082-CS-0339.mp3)
    - Ambassador Matlock, Background to Western Press, 1987-11-27 (Box AV11, Audio-cassette RL11082-CS-0143)
      - Digital audio file (Digital-materials RL11082-SET-0144, Audio-file RL11082-CS-0143.mp3)
    - Ambassador Backgrounder, Jim Gallagher from the Chicago Tribune, 1987-12-02 (Box AV11, Audio-cassette RL11082-CS-0145)
      - Digital audio file (Digital-materials RL11082-SET-0146, Audio-file RL11082-CS-0145.mp3)
    - Amb. Matlock Backgrounder to U.S. Press, 1988-01-08 (Box AV11, Audio-cassette RL11082-CS-0146)
      - Digital audio file (Digital-materials RL11082-SET-0147, Audio-file RL11082-CS-0146.mp3)
    - Amb. Matlocker Backgrounder to U.S. Press (cont'd), 1988-01-08 (Box AV11, Audio-cassette RL11082-CS-0147)
      - Digital audio file (Digital-materials RL11082-SET-0148, Audio-file RL11082-CS-0147.mp3)
    - Amb. Matlock Western Press Brief, 1988-01-29 (Box AV11, Audio-cassette RL11082-CS-0148)
      - Digital audio file (Digital-materials RL11082-SET-0149, Audio-file RL11082-CS-0148.mp3)
    - Ambassador Matlock Backgrounder Press Briefing, 1988-02-05 (Box AV11, Audio-cassette RL11082-CS-0150)
      - Digital audio file (Digital-materials RL11082-SET-0151, Audio-file RL11082-CS-0150.mp3)
    - Matlock Press Brief, 1988-02-12 (Box AV11, Audio-cassette RL11082-CS-0151)
      - Digital audio file (Digital-materials RL11082-SET-0152, Audio-file RL11082-CS-0151.mp3)
    - Ambassador Press Brief, 1988-02-19 (Box AV11, Audio-cassette RL11082-CS-0152)
      - Digital audio file (Digital-materials RL11082-SET-0153, Audio-file RL11082-CS-0152.mp3)
    - Ambassador Press Brief, 1988-03-04 (Box AV11, Audio-cassette RL11082-CS-0161)
      - Digital audio file (Digital-materials RL11082-SET-0162, Audio-file RL11082-CS-0161.mp3)
    - Ambassador Pres Brief-Mark Ramee, 1988-04-01 (Box AV11, Audio-cassette RL11082-CS-0159)
      - Digital audio file (Digital-materials RL11082-SET-0160, Audio-file RL11082-CS-0159.mp3)
    - Ambassador Matlock Backgrounder to U.S. Press, 1988-04-08 (Box AV11, Audio-cassette RL11082-CS-0158)
      - Digital audio file (Digital-materials RL11082-SET-0159, Audio-file RL11082-CS-0158.mp3)
    - Amb. Press Brief at USCO -Western Press, 1988-04-16 (Box AV11, Audio-cassette RL11082-CS-0157)
      - Digital audio file (Digital-materials RL11082-SET-0158, Audio-file RL11082-CS-0157.mp3)
    - Side A: Новое время Shultz; Side B: Codel Johnston at Pravda, 1988-04-22; 1988-04-06 (Box AV14, Audio-cassette RL11082-CS-0260)
      - Digital audio file (Digital-materials RL11082-SET-0261, Audio-file RL11082-CS-0260.mp3)
    - Secretary of State Shultz Remarks in Kiev, 1. Consulat 2. Babiy Yan 3. Pechasky Monastery--missing beginning, 1988-04-23 (Box AV08, Audio-cassette RL11082-CS-0041)
      - Digital audio file (Digital-materials RL11082-SET-0042, Audio-file RL11082-CS-0041.mp3)
    - Amb. Matlock Backgrounder to U.S. Press, 1988-04-29 (Box AV11, Audio-cassette RL11082-CS-0156)
      - Digital audio file (Digital-materials RL11082-SET-0157, Audio-file RL11082-CS-0156.mp3)
    - Matlock Press Briefing, 1988-05-13 (Box AV11, Audio-cassette RL11082-CS-0155)
      - Digital audio file (Digital-materials RL11082-SET-0156, Audio-file RL11082-CS-0155.mp3)
    - Ambassador Briefing, 1988-05-20 (Box AV11, Audio-cassette RL11082-CS-0154)
      - Digital audio file (Digital-materials RL11082-SET-0155, Audio-file RL11082-CS-0154.mp3)
    - AMB Briefing Final Remarks, 1988-06-03 (Box AV12, Audio-cassette RL11082-CS-0190)
      - Digital audio file (Digital-materials RL11082-SET-0191, Audio-file RL11082-CS-0190.mp3)
    - Ambassador Press Conference/Brief, 1988-06-03 (Box AV12, Audio-cassette RL11082-CS-0201)
      - Digital audio file (Digital-materials RL11082-SET-0202, Audio-file RL11082-CS-0201.mp3)
    - Recording of Stockholm-Helsinki, June 15, 1988 Video Press Conf. with Ambassador Matlock, 1988-06-15 (Box AV20, Video-cassette RL11082-VHS-0233)
    - Ambassador Press Brief-NOB, 1988-06-17 (Box AV12, Audio-cassette RL11082-CS-0198)
      - Digital audio file (Digital-materials RL11082-SET-0199, Audio-file RL11082-CS-0198.mp3)
    - Ambassador Press Brief, International Press, 1988-06-24 (Box AV12, Audio-cassette RL11082-CS-0199)
      - Digital audio file (Digital-materials RL11082-SET-0200, Audio-file RL11082-CS-0199.mp3)
    - Ambassador's Press Briefing, 1988-07-01 (Box AV12, Audio-cassette RL11082-CS-0202)
      - Digital audio file (Digital-materials RL11082-SET-0203, Audio-file RL11082-CS-0202.mp3)
    - Ambassador Matlock on the Record and Background, 1988-07-08 (Box AV12, Audio-cassette RL11082-CS-0193)
      - Digital audio file (Digital-materials RL11082-SET-0194, Audio-file RL11082-CS-0193.mp3)
    - Ambassador Matlock's Press Briefing, 1988-07-22 (Box AV12, Audio-cassette RL11082-CS-0194)
      - Digital audio file (Digital-materials RL11082-SET-0195, Audio-file RL11082-CS-0194.mp3)
    - Amb. Matlock Backgrounder, 1988-08-05 (Box AV12, Audio-cassette RL11082-CS-0188)
      - Digital audio file (Digital-materials RL11082-SET-0189, Audio-file RL11082-CS-0188.mp3)
    - Ambassador Matlock Backgrounder, 1988-08-12 (Box AV12, Audio-cassette RL11082-CS-0195)
      - Digital audio file (Digital-materials RL11082-SET-0196, Audio-file RL11082-CS-0195.mp3)
    - Ambassador Matlock's Backgrounder with Christof Bertrand of "Die Zeit", 1988-08-15 (Box AV12, Audio-cassette RL11082-CS-0196)
      - Digital audio file (Digital-materials RL11082-SET-0197, Audio-file RL11082-CS-0196.mp3)
    - Matlock Press Brief, 1988-08-19 (Box AV12, Audio-cassette RL11082-CS-0197)
      - Digital audio file (Digital-materials RL11082-SET-0198, Audio-file RL11082-CS-0197.mp3)
    - Amb.--Press Brief, 1988-08-26 (Box AV12, Audio-cassette RL11082-CS-0189)
      - Digital audio file (Digital-materials RL11082-SET-0190, Audio-file RL11082-CS-0189.mp3)
    - Ambassador Matlock Backgrounder to U.S. and Western Press, 1988-09-30 (Box AV12, Audio-cassette RL11082-CS-0185)
      - Digital audio file (Digital-materials RL11082-SET-0186, Audio-file RL11082-CS-0185.mp3)
    - Ambassador Matlock Backgrounder on Plenum (Side A), Shawn Byrnes on Background on Plenum (Side B), 1988-10-01; 1988-10-01 (Box AV12, Audio-cassette RL11082-CS-0186)
      - Digital audio file (Digital-materials RL11082-SET-0187, Audio-file RL11082-CS-0186.mp3)
    - Press Briefing by DCM Mike Joyce, 1988-10-14 (Box AV09, Audio-cassette RL11082-CS-0089)
      - Digital audio file (Digital-materials RL11082-SET-0090, Audio-file RL11082-CS-0089.mp3)
    - Joyce-Amb. Matlock Press Briefing, 1988-11-04 (Box AV09, Audio-cassette RL11082-CS-0090)
      - Digital audio file (Digital-materials RL11082-SET-0091, Audio-file RL11082-CS-0090.mp3)
    - Amb. Matlock's Press Briefing, 1988-12-02 (Box AV09, Audio-cassette RL11082-CS-0094)
      - Digital audio file (Digital-materials RL11082-SET-0095, Audio-file RL11082-CS-0094.mp3)
    - Ambassador Matlock Briefing, 1988-12-30 (Box AV10, Audio-cassette RL11082-CS-0104)
      - Digital audio file (Digital-materials RL11082-SET-0105, Audio-file RL11082-CS-0104.mp3)
    - Ambassador Matlock Press Briefing, 1989-01-13 (Box AV09, Audio-cassette RL11082-CS-0096)
      - Digital audio file (Digital-materials RL11082-SET-0097, Audio-file RL11082-CS-0096.mp3)
    - Amb. Matlock Backgrounder to US Press, 1989-01-20 (Box AV10, Audio-cassette RL11082-CS-0106)
      - Digital audio file (Digital-materials RL11082-SET-0107, Audio-file RL11082-CS-0106.mp3)
    - Amb. Matlock Press Briefing, 1989-02-03 (Box AV09, Audio-cassette RL11082-CS-0093)
      - Digital audio file (Digital-materials RL11082-SET-0094, Audio-file RL11082-CS-0093.mp3)
    - Amb. Matlock Press Briefing, 1989-02-17 (Box AV09, Audio-cassette RL11082-CS-0095)
      - Digital audio file (Digital-materials RL11082-SET-0096, Audio-file RL11082-CS-0095.mp3)
    - Amb. Matlock with Soviet Press, 1989-02-22 (Box AV09, Audio-cassette RL11082-CS-0099)
      - Digital audio file (Digital-materials RL11082-SET-0100, Audio-file RL11082-CS-0099.mp3)
    - Amb. Matlock Press Brief--US and Western, 1989-02-24 (Box AV09, Audio-cassette RL11082-CS-0100)
      - Digital audio file (Digital-materials RL11082-SET-0101, Audio-file RL11082-CS-0100.mp3)
    - Ambassador Matlock Backgrounder with Expulsion, 1989-03-10 (Box AV09, Audio-cassette RL11082-CS-0101)
      - Digital audio file (Digital-materials RL11082-SET-0102, Audio-file RL11082-CS-0101.mp3)
    - Amb. Matlock Press Brief, 1989-03-24 (Box AV09, Audio-cassette RL11082-CS-0102)